OK，我们说到哪儿了？
OK, where was I?
你在跟我们说你和妈妈是怎么认识的
You were telling us how you met mom
而且真是折腾人的细节化
and that excruciating detail.
没错，要回溯到2005年,我还是27岁的时候
Right. So back in 2005 when I was 27
我最好的两个朋友订婚了
my two best friends got engaged.
这触动了我，也许我也该结婚了
And that got me thinking. Maybe I should get married.
这时我看见了Robin
And then I saw Robin.
她真是太美了
She was incredible.
我打心底里想要认识她
I just knew I had to meet her.
于是你们的Barney叔叔出现了
That's where your uncle Barney came in.
我提议玩一个游戏，我愿意称之为……
I suggest we play a little game I'd like to call
“你见过Ted没有”
'have you met Ted?'
什么，不，我们不玩这游戏
No, we are not playing 'have you met Ted.'
嗨，你见过Ted没有？
Hi, have you met Ted?
接着我们约会了
So I asked her out.
我知道这听起来有点疯狂……
And I know that sounds crazy,
但只经过了一次约会abc我就爱上她了
but just after one date, I was in love with her.
也让我说了一句不该说的话……
which made me say something stupid.
我想我爱上你了
I think I'm in love with you.
什么？
What?
哦，老爸……
Oh, dad!
然后怎么样了？
So then, what happened?
什么也没发生
Nothing.
我是说，我那一次实在太笨了
I mean, I'd made a complete fool of myself.
所以那次之后，我决定不再给她打电话了
So a week went by, and I decided not to call her.
这么说你不打算给她打电话了
So you're not going to call her?
你从“我想我爱上你了”转变成“我不会给她电话了”？
You went from "I think I'm in love with you" to "I'm not going to call her?"
我没有爱上她好吗？
I wasn't in love with her, OK?
我只是爱上了“结婚”这个抽象概念
I was briefly in love with the abstract concept of getting married.
这跟Robin没关系
That's absolutely nothing to do with Robin.
-Robin？-嘿
-Robin?-Hey!
瞧瞧我碰见谁了
Look who I ran into!
你们俩什么时候认识的？
Since when do you guys know each other?
大概在这里的时候吧
Since about here.
Lily认出我是新闻主播了，所以……
Lily recognized me from the news in that ...
悠着点，水手
Hello, sailor!
他们刚刚订婚
They've just engaged.
我该回台里去了，回头见
I should get back to the station. See you guys!
-很高兴见到你，Ted-是啊，我也是
-Nice to meet you, Ted.-Yeah, you, too.
-糟糕！-怎么了？
-Damn it!-What?
我真的爱上她了
I'm in love with her.
不行！
No!
作为你的顾问，我可不想你一错再错,你这次搞砸了，故事结束，继续前进吧
As your sponsor, I will not let you relapse. You blew it. It's over. Move on!
我不知道，我就是有这样的感觉,她就是未来的Ted Mosbie夫人
I don't know. I just have this feeling: she's the future Mrs. Ted Mosbie.
Lily，你刚才尖叫了
Lily, you squeaked?
她跟你谈起我了，是不是？
She said something about me, didn't she?
说出来吧，告诉我！
Come on! Spill it.
好吧
Fine.
嗯，你觉得Ted怎么样？
So, what do you think of Ted?
他是个“例外”
Ted's something else.
我觉得这是褒义的
I'm going to spin that is good.
别的男性都常例，而我是“例外”
Lots of guys are something. I'm something else.
有些过于主动了
Comes a little strong.
但……这也算我的魅力吧
But that's part of my charm.
但……这也算他的魅力吧
But that's part of his charm.
哦，那是当然，我是说,他很体贴，很有魅力，只是……
Oh, totally. I mean, he's sweet, he's charming, he's just
他想要的东西比我想要的更郑重一些
looking for something a little bit more serious than I am.
我说，我现在需要的，是随性一点的关系
I mean, the most I can handle now is something casual.
这些话你不会外传的吧？
This stays between us, right?
开什么玩笑，这两片唇闭得紧紧的
Are you kidding? This flapper afford knocks.
Oops……
她想要随性一点，好的,我可以很随性
She wants casual. OK, I'll be casual.
This flapper afford knocks.
我现在就是一颗“随性”号原子弹
I'm going to be a mushroom cloud of casual.
你知道为什么吗？
You know why?
因为这是个游戏,我是很想直达最后幸福圆满的结局
Because it's a game. I want to escape to the end and do the whole happily-ever-after thing.
但是你必须先玩游戏过关，才能有大结局
But you don't get there unless you play the game.
那么你要约她出来了？
So you're going to ask her out?
是的……不！
Yeah! No!
我不能约她出来，因为如果我约她出来,我就是在约她出来了
I can't ask her out. If I ask her out, I'm asking her out.
所以我怎么能约她出来，而又没有约她出来呢？
So how do I ask her out without asking her out?
你们几个家伙是不是抽大烟了？
Did you guys get high?
我有主意了，我们不约会
I got it. I don't ask her out.
我要请她来参加我们下周五的派对
I invite her to our party next Friday.
-我们下周五要开派对？-刚刚决定的
-We're having a party next Friday?-We are now.
“随性”
Casual.
是啊，没有比“找来一百个人开派对，就是为了泡一个mm”更随性的了，哦，Lily……
Yeah, because nothing is just casual like inviting a hundred people over just to meet on one girl. Oh, and Lily.
那是我的腿
That's my leg.
你过了5分钟才告诉我？
You waited 5 minutes to tell me that?
好的，给她打电话吧
Alright, so call her up.
不，打电话一点也不“随性”,我得和她在什么地方偶遇
No, calling's not casual. I should get bumped into somewhere.
真希望我有她行程表,我就能安排一次偶然的邂逅了
If only I knew her schedule I could arrange a chance encounter.
说得好，你就成了最最随性的跟踪者了
That's great, Ted. You'll be the most casual stalker ever.
自从戴上Marshal送的戒指之后……
Now ever since Marshal put that ring on her finger
Lily变得有点……嗯……贪心
Lily had been, well, extra affectionate
宝贝，现在不行……
Baby, no!
我周日要交一篇关于宪法的25页的论文,我才刚刚开始写
I have a 25-page paper on constitution. I'll due Monday. I barely started.
我只不过是坐在这儿……
I am just sitting here.
戴着手上的戒指
wearing my ring
我漂亮的戒指啊
my beautiful ring
让我身上别的东西有点不对劲了
kinda makes wearing other stuff seem wrong.
我的衬衫……我不想再穿了
My shirt. Kinda don't want to wear my shirt anymore.
或者……我的内衣
or my underwear.
哦，对了，我没穿内衣
That's right. I'm not wearing any.
-没穿内衣？-一点也没穿
-No underwear.-Not even slightly.
两位……
Guys!
有个限度
Boundaries.
她在那！
谢谢你，Bill
Thanks, Bill.
我现在在Colombus大街75号abcrazzle dazzle超市为您报道
I'm reporting from the Razzle Dazzle Supermarket on 75th in Colombus.
Colombus大街75号
75th in Colombus.
好戏开始！
Game on!
4岁的Neroy Alenberg爬进了一台抓公仔机并受困其中……
There she is.\nA 4-year-old Nebroy Alenberg has climbed inside a grab-a-prize machine and got him stuck
仅仅为了得到一个紫色的长颈鹿
and on the pursuit of a stuffed purple giraffe.
都市新闻一台为您报道,我是Robin Trabonski
Metro News 1. I'm Robin Trabowski.
Ted？
Ted?
Robin，哇，这巧啊
Robin? Wow, what are the odds!
你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing here?
哦，我是来买东西的……买调味酱
Oh, you know, just shopping for dip.
我爱调味酱
I love dip.
不，我不爱调味酱,我只是喜欢调味酱，朋友之间的那种
Not I love dip. I like dip, as a friend, you know.
对了，你是在这报道什么新闻吗？
Hey, you're reporting a news story or something?
是啊，一个小孩捆在抓公仔机里了,如果你愿意称之为新闻的话
Yeah, kid's stuck in a cream machine. How sweet of you to call it news.
哦，小孩捆在抓公仔机里了
Wow, kid in a cream machine.
你是真的很想要那个玩具咯,不想遵循常规
You just said to have that toy, didn't you? Couldn't play the game like everyone else.
你浑身都是汗
You're all sweaty.
孩子真可爱
Cool kid.
话说回来，既然这么巧遇见你,我们下周五要举办一个派对
It was so funny I should run into you. We're having a party next Friday
如果你有兴趣来的话，不过“不必太认真”
If you like swinging by. But you know, whatever.
哦，我下周末要回家
Oh, I'm going back home next weekend.
真可惜不是今晚
It's too bad it's not tonight.
是的，就是今晚
It is. It's tonight.
这周五，我说了下周五吗？
This Friday. Did I say next Friday?
是的，我很抱歉,大概是整个星期都在说“下周五”
Yes, sorry. I've been, I guess, I've been saying 'next Friday' all week.
不过，派对就是今晚，不过“不必太认真”
But, yes, tonight. The party's tonight. But you know, whatever.
喂
Hello.
嘿，我打搅到你吗？
Hey, am I interrupting anything?
没有，我还在写论文，啃书本
No, now I'm just writing my paper.
是啊，嗯，你和Lily也许该穿好衣服了
Yeah, well, you and Lily may want to put some clothes on.
我们两个小时之内要开派对,好的，拜
We're throwing a party in 2 hours. OK, bye.
那么，兄弟，Robin出现你打算怎样
So, what are you going to do when Robin shows up?
好的，我的计划好了
OK, I got it all planned out.
她走进门来
She steps through the door.
Ted在哪儿？并不是焦急的等候在门口
And where is Ted? Not eagerly wait by the door.
我在房子的另一边，给一个惹火的姑娘展示我的建筑画图的工具
Now I'm across the room at my drafting table showing some foxy young thing all my cool architecture stuff.
Robin走了过来，我很随性的跟她说……
So Robin throws her over and I casually give her one of these.
嘿，你好啊
Hey, what's up?
然后她说，嘿，地方不错啊
She says, 'hey,nice place. etc. etc.'
然后我再说
Then I say,
那就别客气，把这里当你自己家吧
'well, make yourself at home.'
然后我就很随性的重新和别人聊天去了
And I casually return to my conversation.
接着，一个小时后
Then, an hour later,
哦，你还在啊
'oh, you're still here?'
我很不经意的这么说
I say, like I don't really care.
不过这也是个不错的开头,然后，我非常随性的……
But it's a nice surprise and then very casually,
向上房顶看看吗？
'wanna see the roof?'
-房顶……-带上房顶后，房顶会帮我料理好一切的
-The roof!-You got to run up to the roof. And the roof takes care of the rest.
这房顶有什么特别的
What's so special about the roof?
哦，月亮，星光，朦胧的远景
Oh, the moon, stars, the shimmering skylight.
在那个房顶上，你不可能不陷入爱河
You cannot fall in love on that roof.
我们还在上面“玩”过几次
We do it up there sometimes.
计划很周详，我的小朋友
Solid plan, my little friend.
我们身高差不多……
We were the same plate.
不过让我提个小小的改动
But may I suggest one little modification?
和你聊天的那个惹火的MM把她带上房顶去，两个人干柴烈火
That foxy young thing that you were chatting up? Take her up to the roof and have sex with her,
-疯狂的猴猴姿势……-这不是原计划！
-crazy monkey style..-That's not the plan!
这才应该是原计划,你瞧瞧她
That should be the plan. I mean, look at her!
Ted，你瞧瞧她,惹火的都冒烟了
Ted, look at her! She's smoking!
谢谢
Thank you!
但她不是Robin
But she's not Robin.
这就是问题所在,Ted，你听我说
Exactly. Ted, let's rap.
统计学上来讲，在纽约的每一个派对上都会有这样一个小妞，她根本不知道这是谁开的派对
Statistic. At every New York party, there's always a girl who has no idea who's party she's at.
她根本不认识你周围的任何人,你也不会再见到她第二次了
She knows no one you know and you will never see her again.
你明白……我的意思吗,这个提议怎么样？
Do you see where I'm going? How is this?
Barney，我不这么觉得……
Barney, I don't think so.
潜望中……
Scoping.
继续潜望……
天啊，你真口耐
Man, you are a dork.
目标锁定
Target acquired.
现在我们来玩个小游戏,我愿意称之为……
And now it's time we play a little game I'd like to call'have you met Ted.'
-“你见过Ted吗？”-哦，别这样，又来……
-'have you met Ted.'-Oh, come on. Not this.
嗨，你见过Ted没有？
Hi, have you met Ted?
没有
No.
-你好-你好
Hi.Hi.
你认识Marshal和Lily吗？
You know Marshal and Lily?
不认识
No.
这个派对里面你都认识谁啊？
Do you know anyone at this party?
我和Carlos一起来的
I work with Carlos.
稍等……
Excuse me.
你们谁认识Carlos？
Anyone know a Carlos?
不认识
No.
银质大盘送上的……大肥肉
On a silver platter bone appetite.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
你放弃，我上场
You are loss or gain.
对不起，我能带你去看看房顶吗？
Excuse me, can I show you the roof?
-上面的美景很迷人-好啊
-It's magical up there.\n-Sure.
等等，嘿，房顶我预订了
Wait. Hey, I got that roof reserved.
Robin不会来了
Dude, Robin's not coming.
嘿，她会出现的！
She'll show up.
她会来的
Hey, she's going to show up.
她没有来
She didn't show up.
至少我们开了一个很棒的派对
At least it was a great party.
我吃完了4大罐调味酱
I ate, like, 4 cans of dip.
你总是知道怎么安慰我，老朋友
You always know what to say, old friend.
是Robin
It's Robin.
-接啊-不不不，我不能马上接
-Answer it.\n-No, not right away.
我要显得随性一些
I got to seem casual.
喂
Hello.
真的很抱歉，我错过了你的派对
I'm so sorry I missed your party.
你是哪位？Meredith？
Who's this? Meredith?
Robin\nRobin.
哦，Robin，嘿,是啊是啊
Oh, Robin! Hey, yeah.
看样子你没能来，是不？
I guess you never showed up, did you?
没有，我被工作缠住了,不过……
No, I got stuck at work but
他们总算把那小孩从机器里弄出来了
they finally got that kid out of the cream machine.
他能保留那个紫色的长颈鹿吗？
Did he get to keep the purple giraffe?
是的，那孩子可以拿走全部的玩具
Yeah, they let him keep all the toys.
他困在里面太久了,都热出疹子了
He was in there a long time and little kids have small bladders.
真希望你的派对是今天就好了
I wish your party was tonight.
没错，派对就是今晚
It is. The party's tonight.
是啊，这个派对要开两天,这才是我们的风格
Yeah, it's a two-day party. Because that's how we roll.
所以，你想不想顺道来玩玩,随性就好
So, if you want to swing by? You know, it's casual.
今晚见
See ya.
是Robin打来的
So that was Robin.
-你为什么这么做，我还有一篇论文要写呢-我知道，我很抱歉，这很糟糕
-What are you doing to me? I've got a paper to write.\n-I know. I'm sorry it's terrible.
-我会给你买更多的调味酱的-Ted!
-I'll buy more dip.\n-Ted!
Ted，等等！！
Ted, wait!
我要法国洋葱口味的！
Get French onion.
你看这个人，我还有论文要写呢
Can you believe this guy? I've got a paper to write.
好吧好吧，但一定要迅速完事
OK, fine. But it's got to be like super quick
而且事后也不能有拥抱
and no cuddling after.
我是最幸运的女孩儿……
I'm the luckiest girl alive.
你说的房顶真是太对了
You were so right about the roof.
那房顶，那房顶是超级催化剂
The roof, the roof is on fire, Ted.
昨晚那小妞……
The girl from last night
我把她带回家了，今天早上送她出来,带着绕了几圈，接着送她走了
I took her back to my place then this morning took her outside, spun her around a couple of times, and sent her walking.
她绝对找不到回来的路了,而她就在那儿！
She will never find her way back and there she is!
她怎么过来的，你邀请她来了？
How did she get here? Did you inviter her?
我不认识她
I've no idea who that is.
她说她是和Carlos一起来的，Carlos是谁？
She said she worked with Carlos. Who's Carlos?
我不知道谁是Carlos
I don't know any Carlos.
嗨，是你啊
Hi, you.
你回来了
You're back.
当然了
I sure am.
来吧，亲爱的，我想喝两杯
Come on, sweetie, I need to drink.
亲爱的？真的？
Sweetie? Really?
哦，兔子们，别这样,房顶我预订了
Oh, rabbits, come on! I got that roof reserved.
我和“和Carlos一起来”的小妞的关系吹了
So it's over between me and worked-with-Carlos girl.
哦，很快啊
Oh, that was fast.
是啊，我一直在找一个甩掉刚认识的小妞的办法
Yeah, I was trying to think what's the quickest way to get rid of a girl you just met.
-我想我爱上你了-什么？
-I think I'm in love with you.\n-What?
谢谢你，伙计
Thanks, bro.
我很乐意帮忙
Glad I could help.
怎么……
What the ...
不不不，不能这样！
对不起，Ted
Sorry, Ted.
太好了，现在Robin来了我怎么办？
Wait, what I'm going to do when Robin shows up?
她会来的！
She'll show up.
她没有来
She didn't show up.
现在好了，我们开了两场派对
Alright, we threw two parties.
每个人都开心了
Everybody had fun.
每个人都享受了，每个人都舒坦了
Everybody wanned. Everybody chant.
现在小孩子该干正事了
And now the kid's got to get to work.
而且这个小孩子不能被打搅,跟我一起说
And the kid is not to be disturbed. Repeat after me
我不会和Marshal嘿咻
I will not have sex with Marshal.
Robin打来的
It's Robin.
喂
Hello.
-嗨，Ted？-Amanda？
-Hi, Ted.\n-Amanda?
哦，Dannis，对不起,你听起来真像Amanda
Oh, Dannis. Sorry, you totally sounded like Armanda.
我是Robin
It's Robin.
哦，Robin
Oh, Robin.
你好
Hi.
我真的很想来
I totally wanted to come.
我又被工作缠住了,感觉就像住在办公室一样
I got stuck at work again. I feel like I live there.
很抱歉，再次缺席你的派对
Sorry to miss your party again.
（西班牙语？）
我怎么了？
Who am I?
我知道你的两天派对不可能再延长到三天了
I guess there is no chance you two-dayer turned into a three-dayer.
不，又延长了,派对今晚照旧
You didn't need. The party continues tonight.
是啊……
yeah.
昨晚上，大家都在喊“继续吧，派对专家”
Last night, people were like,"Keep it going, bro! Party trifecta! "
哇哦，很好啊，我会来的
OK, I'll be there.
很好，今晚见
Great. See you tonight.
Robin打来的
So that was Robin.
于是，我为Robin开了第三个派对……在周日的晚上
So I threw a third party for Robin on a Sunday night.
真够无趣的
Oh, this is lame.
无趣，还是随性？
Lame or casual?
-无趣-或是随性
-Lame.\n-Or casual.
对不起，宝贝，我要工作,我需要血液集中在这儿
-Sorry, baby, I got to work. I need all my blood up here.
有没有人见到一本《1865-1923雕塑赔偿合同导论》？
Has anybody seen 'an Introduction to Contract toward Restitution Statutes from 1865 to 1923?'
有没有人看见一本又大又厚的书？
Anybody seen a big ass book?
你好，Barney
Hello, Barney.
哦，当然了
Oh, of course.
你看起来不错
You look well
真奇怪，他们把我们俩都邀请来了
Is it weird they invited both of us?
谁？
Who?
谁会邀请你？没有人认识你
Who invited you? No one even knows who you are!
我明白你很受伤，但是……
I understand you are hurt. But
你不用说的这么绝吧
you don't have to be cruel.
Carlos说得对
Carlos was right about you.
谁是Carlos？
Who is Carlos?
好吧，我的
好吧，到底上哪儿找我的……
OK, where the hell is my...
好吧
OK.
《1865-1923雕塑赔偿合同导论》……
'an Introduction to Contract toward Restitution Statutes from 1865 to 1923'
不是一个杯垫！
is not a coaster!
Ted，我在拿我的法律生涯开玩笑就为了你能开，不是一个……
Ted, I'm jeopardizing my law careers so you can throw not one,
不是两个，而是三个派对就为了某个姑娘
not two, but three parties for some girl
你们不过刚刚认识，她甚至不一定来
that you just met who's probably never going to show up.
我说，她在哪儿，Ted？
I mean where is she, Ted?
Robin在哪儿？
Where is Robin?
嗨……嗨，Robin
Hi, Robin.
这么说，你开了这么多派对就为了我？
So you threw all these parties for me?
不，你这么想，当然不……
No, oh, you thought that. No!
好吧，我承认，你抓到我了
OK, yes, you got me.
我开这些派对的原因之一就是想给你介绍……
One of the reasons I threw these parties was so that I could introduce you to
这个人
This guy.
我想，既然我们之间没戏了,我们可以一笑忘之
I figured, you know, since it didn't work out between us, now we can just laugh about it.
不管怎么说，Robin，这位是……
Anyway, Robin, this is
Carlos\nCarlos.
她还在和Carlos聊着
She's still talking to Carlos.
我还有希望，这还不是最后
I can still win this, it's not over.
好吧，伙计，是时候讲清楚了
OK, buddy. It's time for the tough talk.
Robin确实是好姑娘,但我们要面对现实
Robin seems great. But let's look at the fact.
你想要结婚，而现在纽约城里有成千上万的姑娘在寻找你
You want to get married. And right now there are a million women looking for exactly you.
只是Robin不是她们中的一员
But Robin ain't one of them.
她不是其中一员,她就是我的另一半！
She's not just one of them. She's the one!
是吗，你的另一半要上房顶了
Yeah. Well, 'the one' is heading up to 'the roof.'
你想怎么办？
What are you going to do?
什么也不做
Nothing.
这个恋爱游戏，我必须玩下去
It's a game. I gotta just keep playing.
-嘿？abc-嘿！
-Hey.
Carlos，我能不能和她单独谈谈
Carlos, can you give us some minute?
没问题
Hey, no sweet ombre.
再见
See ya.
Robin\nRobin,
听着，我开这个派对不是为了给你介绍Carlos
look, I didn't throw this party to set you up with Carlos.
前一个也不是，前前一个也不是
Or the one before that. Or the one before that.
我开这些派对，就想见见你
I threw these parties because I wanted to see you.
那么我现在来了
Well, here I am.
我们之间肯定有些什么,要不我就是疯了
There's something here unless I'm crazy.
你没有疯
You're not crazy.
我不知道，Ted，我是说我们才刚刚认识
I don't know, Ted. We barely know each other.
而且你一直用那种眼神看着我就好像……
And you're looking at me with that look and it's like
-像什么？-就好像……
-Like what?\n-Like.
就好像……我们恋爱吧……
Like 'let's fall in love,
然后结婚，然后生小孩,再送他们去足球学校
and get married and have kids and drive them to soccer practice.'
除非他们自己有兴趣,不然我不会强迫小孩去运动的
I'm not going to force sports on them unless they're interested.
这个眼神很好，可惜对象错了
It's a great look. But you're looking at the wrong girl.
-不，没有abc-是的，你找错人了
-No, I'm not.\n-Yes, you are.
我现在不想结婚，也许永远都不会
I don't want to get married right now, maybe never.
如果我们在一起了，我觉得……
If we got together I'd feel like
就好像我不是嫁给你，就是伤你的心
I'd either have to marry you or break your heart.
而这两个，我都没法做到
I just couldn't do either of those things,
就像你也做不到“关掉”你对我的感觉一样
just like you can't turn off the way you feel.
关掉了，我们嘿咻吧
Click off, let's make out.
什么？
What?
怎么了，就是感情开关了
What? That was the off switch.
我把它关了
And I turned it off.
我是说，没错，我是想谈恋爱,结婚，Blah，Blah，Blah
I mean, sure, yes. I want to fall in love, get married, blah, blah, blah.
但，另一方面……
But on the other hand,
你，我，还有这房顶
you, me, the roof.
没有这种开关
There is no off switch.
有这种开关
There is an off switch.
而且我把它关了
And it's off.
不，没关
No, it's not
关了
Yes, it is.
-不，还没有-已经……
关了
No, it's not.
不，还没关
你说得对，没有这种开关
You were right. There is no off switch.
天啊，我真希望有这种开关
God, I wish there was an off switch.
我也这么想
Me, too.
那么……
So...
接下来该怎么办
What to do now?
我们可以做好朋友
We could be friends.
听着，我知道人们说这句话的时候听起来都很不真诚，但……
Look, I know it sounds insincere when people say that but.
我们可以做好朋友
we could
我不知道，Robin
I don't know, Robin.
我如今弄得自己像个大傻瓜
I made such a jackass of myself.
如果我们做朋友，每次我看到你我都会想到：“哦，对了，我是个大傻瓜”
If we started hanging out, every time I see you, it will be like, 'Oh, that's right, I'm a jackass.'
你不是傻瓜
You're not a jackass.
我很抱歉，我四月刚刚搬来,而且一直在工作
I'm sorry. I only moved here in April and I'm always working.
我只是到现在朋友圈子也不大
I just haven't met a lot of good people so far.
但我明白你
But I understand.
也许过几个月，这件事都淡化了,我们可以……
Maybe in a few months after it's not so fresh we could all
你知道，一起喝啤酒什么的
you know, get a beer.
是啊，听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds good.
以后再见，Ted
I'll see you, Ted.
又或者，就现在
Or, you know, now.
我们可以现在就去喝点啤酒
We could all get a beer now.
我同意
I'd like that.
我的朋友都会爱上你的
My friends are going to love you.
喜欢你，你知道，朋友之间的那种
Like you, you know, as a friend.
大傻瓜
Jackass!
难以相信
Unbelievable.
简直就是灾难，他们是一起的
That's just a recipe for disarster. They worked together!
你嫉妒了？
You're jealous?
哦，得了吧，有什么Carlos有的我没有？
Oh, please, what does Carlos have that I don't?
他今晚有约会
A date tonight?
说的漂亮，再来一遍
play it again.
（录像倒带）他今晚有约会
A date tonight?
我爱死她了
I'm not sure I like her.
你不是还有论文要写吗？
Hey, don't you have a paper to write?
-伙计，说话也不看对象-我知道
-Dude, you are talking to the kid.\n-I know it.
我先把这杯喝个底朝天,在干了下一杯
I'm going to knock back this beer, I'm going to knock back one more beer.
然后我再回家写一篇25页的论文
We could all get a beer now.\nI'm going to go home. I'm going to write a 25-page paper.
接着交上去，得一个A
I'm going to hand it in and I'm going to get an A.
我的名字是Ruffles，而这就是事实
My name's Ruffith and that's the truffith.
他的论文评价是B减
He got a B minus.
但仍然要说，一夜写出25页的论文,还得了个B减，这家伙很强
But still, 25 pages in one night, B minus? The kid is good.
至少让我请你一杯啤酒
At least let me buy you a beer.
我要请你们每一个人喝一杯
Come on. I'll buy everyone a beer.
我帮你拿
I'll help carry.
-有件事你知道吗，Ted？-什么？
-You know something, Ted?\n-What?
你很有魅力的
You're a catch.
你一定会让某个女孩非常幸福
You're going to make some girl very happy.
而我，要帮你找到这个女孩
And I am going to help you find her.
那，就祝你好运吧
Well, good luck.
我说，也许你的承诺太大了,这个城市里有上百万个女孩子
I mean, maybe New York is too big a town and there's millions of people in the city.
在这么大一堆乱麻里一个男人怎么找到自己的终生伴侣，我是说……
How in all this mess is a guy supposed to find the love of his life? I mean,
该从哪里开始？
Where even begin?
嗨，你认识Ted吗？
Hi, have you met Ted?
Well, good luck.